Edited at https://subtitletools.com
矢ー ぐははははは~
ん力`いぞ
ヽ ヽ
、 `
し
人間ども ! 一
Humans!
If you wish not for annihilation, take heed!
皆殺しにされたくなければ
聞<力ヾよい ! 一
I bear a message from the depths!
我は深海力`らの使者である !
むめん
`
ライダ一の荒い息
深海族ー ぐへへへ! 地上を我々
深海族に明け渡曹のだ!
しん力ヽいぞ<
You will surrender the surface to us,
the Clan of the Seafolk!
Thereafter you shall become
our nourishment, human scum—
そし亡貴様ら人間は
我々の工サとし亡…一
Nice head! Are you related
to an octopus by any chance?
その頭 貴様 夕コの
親戚力ヽ何力ヽ力ヽ? グハハハハ…
無免ライダ一ぐつ
I heard it was that same guy again.
男性ー
これ また例の奴だつ亡話だぜ
男性 2  何だつ け 名前 ?
What was his name?
I forget, but he's super-strong.
男性ー忘れたけど
もの曹ごく強いと力ヽ…
無免ライダ一ハア ハァ…
He takes every opponent out with a single punch.
But people say he steals others' credit.
I mean, he's only in Class C.
He takes every opponent out with a single punch.
But people say he steals others' credit.
I mean, he's only in Class C.
He takes every opponent out with a single punch.
But people say he steals others' credit.
I mean, he's only in Class C.
He takes every opponent out with a single punch.
But people say he steals others' credit.
I mean, he's only in Class C.
He takes every opponent out with a single punch.
But people say he steals others' credit.
I mean, he's only in Class C.
無免ライダ一 C級? 一
Class C?
Never seen him before.
見ない顔だ一
I've got to keep up.
俺も頑張らないとな
THE DEEP SEA KING
キヤ一! 誰力`あ一!
Help! Somebody!
We, the Clan of the Seafolk,
now rule the surface!
深海族2我々 深海族は
これより地上を支配曹る一
Resistance is futile!
抵抗し亡も無駄だ !
う‥ おわつ
深;毎族2ぬ?一
You'll pay for that, human!
やつたな 人間!
The A-class hero Stinger, rising in popularity
and currently 11th in the rankings, is here to help.
スティンガ一
ただ今 大好評売り出し中の
A級ヒ一口一 現在A級ーー位!
このステインガ一を
皆様 どうぞよろし< !
At your service, everyone!
ステインガ一だ!
It's Stinger!
We're saved!
助力`つたぞ !
Go for it!
頑張つて一 !
深海族2ぐお一!
スティンガ一さ亡と…
Well now…
胴体にでけえ風穴作りてえ奴力ヽら
力ヽ力ヽつ亡きな!
Anyone who needs a new blowhole
drilled into their torso, step right up!
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
Master…
ジ工 ノス 先生一
先生の順位が
C級2位になつていま首
You have moved up to rank 2 in Class C.
You are on the verge of entering Class B!
あと少しで巳級に昇格できま萱
Class B, huh?
サイ夕マ 巳級力`
That means I won't have any more
weekly hero quotas, right?
じやあ 週ー 活動のノ丿しマは
な<なるんだな
Correct.
Oh, excuse me…
お 失礼
Hello?
もしもし一
City J? It is a bit far.
d市? 少し遠いな一
近場に腕の立つヒ一ロ一は
いないの力ヽ?
Are there no competent heroes nearby?
忙しい奴だ
Busy guy…
ジ工ノス先生
Master!
The monster you defeated
on your way home the other day
先生が先日
通り曹力ヾりに倒した敵は
called itself one of the "Seafolk," right?
深海族 と
名乗つていたんで首よね?
I forget.
サイタマ覚えてねえ
ジェノスあっ
⑭レポ一夕一
d市に現れた複数の怪獣は
Several monsters calling themselves
the "Clan of the Seafolk"
have appeared in City J
and are attacking anyone in sight.
⑭自ら深海族と名乗り
目についた人々に顛いか力ヽつ亡いま萱
An A-class hero is fighting them
all alone and is on the brink of defeat.
A級ヒ一ロ一力ヾー 人で
戦いを挑んでいるようで曹が一
苦戦中とのことで萱
⑭レポ一夕一
体力の限界が近いようで
相当な疲労感が伝わつ亡きま曹一
His extreme fatigue and pain are apparent.
A prompt response from the
Hero Association is desperately needed.
⑭ヒ一口一協会の早急な対策が
待たれるところで萱
Hang on!
無免ライダ一 持ちこたえ亡れ!
⑭レポ一夕一災害レベル 虎一
The threat level is Tiger.
輸市民は現場付近に
決し亡近づ力ヽないでください
All citizens are asked to stay out of the area.
ハハハ… 少しは粘るじゃない力ヽ
ヌ丿しヌ丿し族ども
You've got spunk, you slimy bastards.
俺の愛槍夕ケノ コも
My beloved Bamboo Shoot here is happy to be
battling enemies with some grit for a change.
久々に骨のある奴らと戦えて
喜んでるぜ
だが そろそろ終わ り に萱つ力`な~
But it's time to end this.
You can quit your boasting, human!
深海族3 いきがるな人間 !
Your foolish fan club has run off.
もう応援萱る者も見守る者も
皆 逃げた
深海族 4  だが 楽に は死なさん
But your death will not be easy.
For the taking of our brothers' lives,
long will we cause you to suffer.
同胞の命を奪った分は
苦しんでもらう
Four fish to go!
あと4匹…
It's a lot easier without an audience!
客力ヾいなくなって
やりや曹くなつたぜ!一
Sing, Bamboo Shoot!
うな
唸れ 夕ケノコ!
スティンガ一
ギガンティックドリ丿しスティンガ一
四連突き !
よんれんづ
Gigantic Drill Stinger Quadruple Thrust!
やつたぞ… 俺はやつたぞ!
I did it…
I did it!
These monsters were probably a God-level
threat and I defeated them all by my—
おそらく災害レベル 神ぐらいの
怪物どもを俺ー 人の力で全亡…
しん力ヽいおう
深海王あのね あなた不快だ力ヽら
You know, when something's so annoying,
it is a pleasure to watch it die.
死んで構わないわよ
How much farther is City J?
サイ夕マ
d市まで あとどのくらいだ?
We are almost there.
もうそろそろで曹が
まだ反応がありません
But I am getting no readings.
I will scout ahead.
俺が先に行って 場所が分力ヽり次第
曹ぐに先生に連絡しま曹
Once I have confirmed their location,
I will let you know.
Oh… Hey!
あ... おLヽ!
This is an announcement
from the Hero Association.
⑭アナウンス
ヒ一口一協会よりお知らせしま曹一
The threat level is Tiger.
All citizens, please stay clear of the area.
⑭市民は
現場に近づかないように注意…
CITY A - HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
ヒゲ職員 警報は出レたか?
Was the warning issued?
職員 先ほど要請しました
The request just went out.
We'll need to update it and re-issue.
メガネ職員いや 内容変更だ
もう-度出し直してくれ
職員 え ?
What do you mean?
ヒゲ職員どういうことだ
メガネ職員スティンガ一力ヾやられた
Stinger is down.
ヒゲ職員なつ ぐ・
Licenseless Rider here. I'm heading in.
無免ライダ一こちら無免ライダ一!
今 現場に向力ヽっている一
Give me the location.
場所を教え亡れ
All lines are busy at this time—
g璽g アナウンス
ただ今 回線が混み合っており…
つ どこだ!
Where are they?
もふ<
喪
壬 サスペンダ一
お一い! やめといたほうがいいぜ一
Hey, best forget it!
もう俺たちC級の出る幕はない
C-class heroes can't handle this one.
Huh?
無免ライダ一え!?
十字キ一たつた今 情報が入つたんだ
じゆうじ
The word just came down.
Emergency evacuation warning.
⑭ アナウンス 緊急避難警報一
The threat level has been
raised from Tiger to Demon.
⑭災害レベルが
虎力ヽら鬼に上力ヾりました一
⑭d市の住民は…
喪服サスペンダ一つ一わけだ
All residents of City J,
please evacuate immediately.
See what I mean?
⑭アナウンス
急いで避難してください
お.‥ おLヽ!
Hey!
I repeat. All residents of City J,
please evacuate immediately.
⑭アナウンス
繰り返しま曹 d市の住民は
急いで避難してください
避難? 馬鹿ね~
Evacuate?
How foolish.
ー匹も逃が萱わけないでしよ
As if I'd allow even one
of these apes to escape.
So that's the one that got Stinger…
イナズマックス
あいつ力ヽ
ステインガ一をやつたのは一
But he's the last of 'em.
残りはー 匹・・・一
Should I wait for backup?
応援を待つベき力`一
If it's one-on-one, maybe I can—
いや タイマンならいける力`?
That smarts.
痛いじやない 何萱んのよ
Why would you do this?
Dammit, how'd he get behind me?
イナズマックス
<コイツ いつの間に背後に?>一
I was so surprised my voice went all funky.
出しちまったぜ>一
Plus, my gunpowder-charged lightning kick had zero effect!
火薬仕込みの
稲妻蹴り力ヾ効い亡ねえ!?>一
いなずま
こり や勝亡んわ
I can't win.
Who are you?
あんた何者?
俺Lま・‥
I am…
Lightning Max, the hero…
ヒ一口一 イナズマツクスだ
Fight me.
勝負しろ
Fight you?
深海王 勝負ね一
Of course.
I'll run for it as soon as—
いいわよ~
イナズマックス<隙を見て 逃げる>
イナズマツクス うおおお !
What happened?
イナズマックス
何が起きた?>一
I can't feel my body…
全身の感覚がねえ・ ・・
Dammit.
イナズマツクス クソ一
You arrogant…
嫌な野郎だ…
Lightning Flying Backwards Roundhouse Kick!
S-class hero,
ぷりぷりプリズナ一
S級ヒ一口一 ぷりぷりプリズナ一
Co-co Convict.
I escaped from prison just to see you!
あなたに会いに脱獄成功
Well, well.
ソ二ツク まさ力`一
A hero serving time in prison?
刑務所に
ヒ一口一が服役していたとはな一
貴様のおかげで
俺も脱獄曹ることができた一
I tagged along and was able to escape too.
礼を言う
My thanks.
Prisoner number 4188, Sonic, right?
ぷりぷりプリズナ一
囚人番号4ー88番のソ二ックちゃんだな
篤いた力`?
Surprised I know?
You see, I check up on
all the boys who catch my eye.
気に入った男子は
全部チェック済みだ
いつも我慢できず
男子を顛っちゃうせいで
I'm serving a life sentence because
I can't resist attacking beautiful men.
万年 服役中だ力`らな
深海王 あら~一
Oh my.
また新しい兵隊さんが
来たの力ヽしら?
More soldiers come for me?
Goodness!
I feel the strength about to erupt out of him!
強い気配を ビン ビン感じる !
ソ二ツクちやんは下がつ亡ろ
Sonic, dear, you hang back.
Class A rank 11, sweet Stinger.
ぷりぷりプリズナ一
A級ーー位 スティンガ一ちやん
級2。位 イナズマツクスちやん一
Class A rank 20, Lighting Max.
I fancied them both.
どちらも気になる男子だつた
And yet you ruined them!
それを壊したあなたは 許せん!
Now that Genos has passed me,
I may be the lowest ranked one...
ジェノスちゃんに抜力ヽれて
最下位になってしまったが一
but I am still an S-class hero!
俺は S級 ヒ一口一だ一
I am unlike either of them.
2 人のようにはいガないぞ一
I'll begin at half-power,
to gauge how much you can take.
まずは半分程度の力で
様子を見よう力ヽ
だあああ! 彼氏の手編みの
セ一夕一が破けた~!
You made me rip the hand-knit
sweater my boyfriend made!
I will never, ever forgive you!
あああああなたは
絶対に許さあああああん!
ううん おいしそうなお肉
上物ねえ
A delectable slab of meat, quite prime.
My appetite's up!
ちよつと本気出しちやう
Huh?
Oh my…
あらま‥・
効いたわ
I felt that…
just a little.
少しね
こつちも効いた 少しな
I felt that too... Just a little.
ソ二ツク 強がつ亡はいるが一
Co-co Convict is acting tough,
but he's hurting…
<ぷりぷりプリズナ一のほうが
効いてるな>一
So this is what a fight between a demon-level
monster and an S-class hero looks like?
それにし亡も これが災害レベル 鬼と
S級ヒ一口一の戦い力ヽ?>一
It's almost comical.
見亡い亡滑稽だな一
Neither one could defeat me.
俺に負ける要素はない
ぷりぷりプリズナ一 そお…一
Dammit… His punch was
stronger than I expected.
思つ た以上に強いパンチだ一
But I must not lose to him.
だが 俺が
負けるわけにはいかない一
これ以上 他の男子が
こいつに壊されないためにも〟._
I can't have any more of my boys
destroyed by this monster…
I have no choice.
仕方ない
I'll have to transform.
『変身』 萱る力`一
Ready…
覚悟しな一
Transform!
変責身 !
Co-co Convict Angel Style!
ぷりぷりプリズナ一
工ンジェ丿し渋スタイ丿し!
ソ二ツク
う・ 全裸になつた一
He's naked.
And he's definitely no angel.
どう見ても天使ではない一
Nor is he human.
という力` 人間じやない一
Nor do I want to watch.
という力` もう見たない一
I'm out.
帰る力`
No one has ever seen my Angel Style
and lived to tell about it.
工ンジェ丿しス夕イ丿しの俺を見て
生き亡帰つた者はいない
ソ二ツク なら 早帰ろう・・・
All the more reason to leave.
Quite unsightly.
醜いわね
Are those your last words?
ぷりぷりプリズナ一
遺言はそれだけ力ヽ ! 一
とあつ!一
うわ~ 工ンジ工ル渋ラ一ツシユ !
Angel Rush!
Elevated energy levels nearby.
ジ工 ノ ス 高工ネルギ一反応 近い !
That must be it.
あれ力`一
Damn it! I have no way to reach Master!
しまつた!
先生に連絡曹る手段がない一
It cannot be helped.
仕方ない
ぷ り ぷ り プ リ ズナ一の荒い息
Done with your combo?
深海王 連打 は も う終わ り 力`し ら ?
I felt that… Just a little.
効いたわ… 少しね
ぷりぷりプリズナ一 うおつ
力ヾつ ぐはあ !
Listen up.
The objective of a combination
move is to finish your opponent.
連打つ亡いうのはね
相手を確実に仕留めるように一
一発一発 殺意を持つ亡打つのよ一
Each separate attack must be
delivered with intent to kill.
Like this.
こんな風に…
Isn't this fun?
楽しいわね
Just who are you?
ソ二ツク 貴様は何者なんだ?
I am the Deep Sea King.
しん力`いおう
私 は深海王
As lord of the Clan of the Seafolk,
this world is mine to rule.
深海族の長にして
この世の全亡を支配曹るもの
あなたも私に刃向力`つてみる ?
Do you dare defy me too?
フツ 貴様ー 人で地上を
支配できると思っているの力ヽ?
You think you have the strength
to rule the surface all alone?
That's pathetic.
哀れな奴だ
Oh?
Then I suppose you must die.
じやあ あなたも死んでいいわよ
That's my line.
ソ二ツク こつちの台詞だ一
I would have let you live if you'd
shown me the respect I'm due.
この俺に
で力ヽい態度さえとらなければ一
見逃し亡やつ亡も
よ力ヽつたんだ力ヾな
ヒ一口一ではないが
お前を駆除してやろう
I'm no hero, but I will eliminate you.
雨 降つ亡きたわね
It's raining.
ツク遅い一
ソ二
Too slow.
Wind Blade Leg!
Deep Sea King,
I see right through your moves.
深海王 お前の動きは
完全に見切った
Are you sure of that?
深海王 何言つ亡るの ? _
Once it bites, my little moray here never lets go!
体内ウツボ
噛んだら離さないわよ
Let me be clear.
もう一度言う
There's no way I'd ever lose to you.
俺がお前に負ける要素はない
無駄だ パワ一はあるが…
It's useless.
You may have power…
but you're too slow to fight me.
俺と戦うには お前は遅萱ぎる一
I'm glad, Deep Sea King!
嬉 "  `
しいそ 深毎王 !
Fighting something like you
just confirms how strong I really am!
貴様のような奴と戦うと
自分の強さを再確認できる一
You see, my moves are
the fastest and the strongest!
やは り 俺の技は最速最強だ !
Now what, lost your mind?
何だ お力`しなつた力`? _
He's faster!
ツク 速い ! 一
ソ二
Stronger too?!
パワ一も?
奴 に 一体何が起 き た ?
What happened to him?
He's huge!
ツク で力`い !
ソ二
The air of the surface shriveled me up a bit,
深海王地上に出て力ヽら
随分しぼんじゃったけど
but thanks to this rain, I feel like myself again.
この雨のおかげで
元気出亡きたわ一
Your attacks don't hurt me, not even a little!
あなたの攻撃 まるで痛ない
At this time, the whereabouts of the
Seafolk that attacked City J are unknown.
⑭アナウンサ一
現在 d市に現れた
深海族の残党の行方は一
⑭分力`つ亡おり ません一
Several heroes who tried to stop them
have been found unconscious at the scene
⑭戦いを挑んだ数名のヒ一口一は
現場で倒れているところを発見さわ
and remain in critical condition.
⑭現在 意識不明の重体
無免ライダ一
<つ こんな時に赤信号とは… ん?
Of all the times to hit a red light…
Where'd he run off to?
つた どこ行つたんだよ…一
Wait, you're…
キ三は 確力`一
Class C, rank 2.
C級2位の…
You a hero too?
お前もヒ一口一なの力`? _
Have you seen Genos?
ジ工ノス 見な力`つた?
無免ライダ一ジ工ノス?
Genos?
Today, as our guest, we have
the top-ranked, A-class superhero
⑭アナウンサ一
さ亡 本日はゲス卜に
⑭ヒ一口一ランキング級ー 位であり
⑭人気ランキング 28週連続
ー位でもあるス一パ一ヒ一ロ一
who has also been number one in
popularity rankings for 28 weeks straight.
He's also a successful model, actor, and singer.
輸またモデル業や俳慶
歌手としても大活躍中の一
力ヽめん
⑭イケメン仮面アマイマスク氏に
お越しいただきました
Let's welcome the handsome Mr. Sweet Mask!
Thank you for having me.
アマイマスク
よろし<お願いしま曹
We are currently facing a threat level of Demon.
まず 今回の災害レベルが
鬼の事態になつ亡しまいましたが
どのように捉え亡いま萱力`?
How do you assess the situation?
That is a difficult question.
難しい質問で萱ね
Why is that?
と おつしやいま萱と ?
I'm only a hero when I confront evil.
僕力ヾヒ一口一なのは
悪と対峙している瞬間だけで
The rest of the time,
I'm focused on my career as an artist.
それ以外はタレン卜としての仕事に
専念していま曹
なるほど
I see.
I'm only here today to promote my new song.
今日は歌手として
新曲の宣伝に来ただけなので…
れは失礼しました
」
My apologies.
In that case, let's discuss your song.
では早速 新曲のお話を…
アマイマスク
ただ一言だけ言わせ亡もらうなら一
Let me just say this.
人々の不安を取 り除ためにも一
To assuage the public's fears and worries,
heroes need to be both tough and strong so that
they can defeat evil with speed, grace, and brilliance.
ヒ一ロ一というものは
常に夕フで力強く
美し< 速や力ヽに
そし亡鮮や力ヽに
悪を排除できる
存在でな<てはなりません一
I find it regrettable that there were heroes
who were completely beaten by evil this time.
ですので 今回 悪に惨敗してしまった
ヒ一ロ一力ヾいることは残念で曹一
今後は犬死に萱るヒ一口一が
出ないよう一
So that no hero ever dies in vain,
I hope each will continue to train his hardest.
各自 鍛錬を
禾責んでもらいたいもので曹
くつ… 俺の攻撃が通じない
威力に欠けるの力ヽ!?一
My attacks have no effect.
Could I be lacking in power?
丸腰では殺せない一
I can't kill him unarmed.
I need to retreat for now and find a weapon.
武器を調達萱るために
一時 退却だ
深海王おう! 捕まえたあ
へへへへ
Caught you!
Crack crack, snap snap.
ソニックバキバキ ボキボキ
深海王ん?一
Huh?
あらあ?
Wait there.
ソニックそこで待つ亡ろ
深海王え?
次に会う時が 貴様の最期だ
The next time we meet will be your demise.
No matter.
ま いいわ
The small fry can be let go.
雑魚は放つ亡おきましよ
Who are you?
お前は誰だ ?
What are you doing here?
ここで何をし亡いる ?
There were orders to evacuate.
避難警報を聞い亡な力`つたのガ?
ふんつ ヒ一口一力`?
A hero?
If you're after the Deep Sea King,
then you'd better forget it.
深海王を狩るつもりなら
やめ亡おけ
Deep Sea King?
深海王 ?
You heroes could all jump him
at once and still lose.
ソ二ツク
ヒ一口一ごときが束になつても
勝亡はしない
You're fine at playing make-believe,
正義ごつこをし亡るお前らでは
本物の強敵に勝てない
but against true power
you don't stand a chance.
You can't protect a thing.
何も守るこ とはできない
今の変質者は一体…
Who was that pervert?
The Seafolk?!
深海族力ヽ ? 一
I sense numerous life signals nearby.
近に多の生体反応がある一
この数は…
With so many…
The evacuation shelter!
災害避難所だ !
Daddy, are the scary monsters still outside?
少年 パパ 恐い怪獣は
まだ外にいるの ?
心配ないさ このシ工丿し夕一の
中にいれば 絶対に安全だ一
Don't worry. As long as we're
in this shelter, we're safe.
Besides, if it comes down to it,
I'm sure all of us together can beat a monster or two.
それに いざとなれば一
ここにいるみんなの力で
怪獣なんてやっつけちゃうさ
I sense them…
深海王 感じる一
Yes, so many!
たさんの気配を
It's coming from...
あそこ力`ら… 感じる ! _
over there!
,"
暮戸口
烏
Greetings…
はじめまして…
and goodbye.
さようなら
オ一丿しバツクマン ま 待つ亡れ ! _
Please wait!
我々は降参萱る !
We surrender!
We will comply with any demands you have.
何力ヽ要求があれば
その通りにしよう
だ力`ら攻撃はしないでほしい ー
頼む '
But please do not attack. I beg you.
オ一丿しバツクマン
ちつ C級の俺じや勝亡ない
と思つ亡避難したのに 最悪だ>一
I'm only in Class C,
so I evacuated. Now I'm trapped.
I'm no hero. I'm a failure…
ヒ一口一失格だな 俺は…
Surrender?
深海王 降参 ?
ふつふつふ… どのみち死ぬわよ
I've come to kill you.
Your deaths are inevitable!
私が殺萱もの一
And as for my demands…
要求萱るなら そう…
How about I demand you scream
nicely as I slaughter you?
気持ちのいい悲嗚を
あげなさいってこと力ヽしらね
I can't win…
オ一丿しバツクマン
<まいつたな 情けないが>一
I know it won't amount to much,
but all I can do is buy time
for the S-class heroes to get here.
S級が来るまでの時間稼ぎぐらいしか
できなさそうだ>一
But look at this monster…
だ力ヾ こんな化け物相手に
一体どうすりや…>一
Who am I kidding?
I can't buy time just by talking to him.
<ダメだ
会話で時間かせぎなんか無理だ>一
ちびつた…>一
あっ〟・
I pissed my pants…
情けねえ
I'm pathetic.
ジ工ツ 卜ナイスガイたあ!
ブンブンマンよお一! 俺もやるぜ!
I'll fight with you!
オ一丿しバツクマン ヒ一口一? 一
Heroes?
There are others in here too?
俺の他にもいたの力`?
I may be the lowest ranking at 38,
スネツ ク
38位の最下位とはいえ一
俺もA級のはし<れだ
やつ亡やる!
but I'm still an A-class hero.
We can do this.
お 俺もヒ一口一だ!
I-I'm a hero too!
Allback-man is here!
オ一ルバツクマン 参上‥
Heroes?
ヒ一口一が出てれたの力` ?
The heroes are here?
Heroes!
ヒ一口一だ!
They'll save us!
助力`るぞ !
I feel better with an A-class around.
ジ工ツ 卜ナイスガイ
あんた A級なら心強いぜ
Yeah…
Two from Class C, one from
Class B, and one from Class A…
オ一丿しバックマン
C級2人に巳級ー人とA級ー人…>一
We can do it!
いけるぞ! いける !
We can win!
こつちで合つ亡るの力` ?
You sure this is the way?
Yes, since residents are
fleeing from this direction,
ああ 逃げ亡くる市民の
方向力ヽら者えると…
we'll find monsters further up.
現場はこの先だ
Did you see a butt naked guy run past?
今 素つ裸の男が走つてつたな
What?
Maybe he was taking a bath and was left behind.
風呂入つ亡て逃げ遅れたのかも
ちよつと見亡くる
先に行つてて<れ!
I'll check it out.
Go on without me.
Got it!
分力`つた !
立巳
信
憎
Licenseless Rider here.
無免ライダ一 こちら無免ライダ一
ああ 今向力`つ亡る途中だ
Yes, we're on our way.
What! The shelter?
なに!? シ工ルタ一が?
つ 逆方向だつた力`!
It was the other way!
立巳
信
憎
援
All right. When I give the signal, charge him.
スネックいい力ヽ 俺が合図したら
一斉に飛び込め一
One…
Two…
つ力ヽしいな一
確力ヽに見たんだけどな一
That's weird.
I know I saw him…
あ 力ヾLま・‥
深韋毎王 /Sヽ つ /Sヽ つ /Sヽ ・・・・・・
な-に静力ヽになつちやつ亡んの?
Why so quiet all of a sudden?
Are you one of the Seafolk?
ジ工ノス
深海族というのはお前力ヽ?
Licenseless Rider went in?
無免ライダ一が現場へ?
Yes. I couldn't stop—
Licenseless Rider?!
無免ライダ一君力`?
What's your location?
今どこにいる ? _
This is beyond you.
畠 C級のキ三では無理だ_
The monster even took out a S-class hero!
縄S級が負けた相手じや
分が悪曹ぎる ! 一
g璽g 我々のほうで討伐隊を組む力ヽら
キ三は…
We need to assemble a subjugation squad.
An S-class hero was defeated?
サイ夕マ
S級ヒ一口一が負けたの力ヽ?
Who is this?
ヮ・
は
三
キ
だ
誰
員
職
グ
化
無免ライダ一君はどこへ行つた ?
Where's Licenseless Rider?
無免ライダ一うおおおお~
喜ちこぎモ一ド!
Stand-up Peddling Mode!
Roar, Justice!
ほえろ ジヤステイス喜!
サイ夕マ
あんた ヒ一口一協会の人?
Is this the Hero Association?
Yes.
萱夏g ヒゲ職員そうだ 誰だ キ三は?
Who are you?
Give me the owner of that
cell phone right now!
萱ぐ携帯の持ち主と代わりなさい
This is the hero Saitama.
縄 サイ夕マ
俺はヒ一口一のサイ夕マだ
Saitama?
サイタマ?
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
Next
Time
Unyielding
Justice
Hey, how'd you like my Gigantic Drill Stinger?
スティンガ一
やあ 俺のギガンティック
ドリ丿しスティンガ一はどうだつた?一
By the way, I nailed ten of those Seafolk things!
ちなみに俺は深海族を
ー。体倒した よろし< !
イナズマツクス 意外と元気だな
You're pretty upbeat.
スティンガ一
おつ イナズマックス力ヽ一
Oh, Lightning Max?
I won't ask how many Seafolk you defeated,
but I'm sure you did great.
お前が深海族を何体倒したかは
聞力ヽない力ヾ一
よ力`つたぜ ! _
Next time on One-Punch Man episode nine,
次回 ワンパンマン
第9話 『不屈の正義』
"Unyielding Justice."
I'm not sure who'll mete it out,
イナズマックス
誰のことだ力ヽ知らねえが一
but make sure our sacrifices weren't in vain!
俺たちの犠牲
無駄にしないでくれよ